Guide to the Freshman Year, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Central records and records of the dean of the Freshman Year, 1920-1964; Series I
  - Treasurer's office (L.G. Tighe), 1946-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1073)
  - Treasurer's office, 1950-1957 (Box 53, Folder 1074 - 1075)
  - Tuition rebates, 1922-1940 (Box 53, Folder 1076 - 1088)
  - Tuition rebates, 1940-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1089 - 1096)
  - U, 1943-1957 (Box 54, Folder 1097)
  - Undergraduate activities, 1945-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1098 - 1105)
  - Undergraduate affairs, 1954-1955 (Box 54, Folder 1106)
  - Undergraduate charges, 1940-1942 (Box 54, Folder 1107 - 1108)
  - Undergraduate catalogue, 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 1109)
  - Undergraduate faculty, 1923-1947 (Box 54, Folder 1110)
  - Undergraduate schedules, 1932-1934 (Box 54, Folder 1111)
  - University development office, 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 1112)
  - University service bureau, 1942-1957 (Box 55, Folder 1113)
  - V, 1920-1933 (Box 55, Folder 1114)
  - Vocational guidance, 1922-1926 (Box 55, Folder 1115)
  - W, 1920-1951 (Box 55, Folder 1116)
  - War articles publications, and memoranda, 1941-1944 (Box 55, Folder 1117)
  - Withdrawals, from the freshman class, 1953-1957 (Box 55, Folder 1118)
  - Minutes - war committee, 1942-1943 (Box 55, Folder 1119)
  - Wood shop, 1956-1957 (Box 55, Folder 1120)
  - X - Y - Z, 1920-1955 (Box 55, Folder 1121)
  - Yale college, 1937-1957 (Box 55, Folder 1122 - 1142)
  - Yale news bureau, 1949-1951 (Box 55, Folder 1143 - 1144)
  - Yale studies, 1944-1947 (Box 55, Folder 1145 - 1147)
  - Air science, 1949-1951 (Box 56, Folder 1148)
  - Athletic department, 1920-1936 (Box 56, Folder 1149 - 1164)
  - Armed services, 1949-1957 (Box 57, Folder 1165)
  - Astronomy department, 1951-1955 (Box 57, Folder 1166)
  - Biology instruction, 1935-1938 (Box 57, Folder 1167)
  - Chemistry department, 1920-1956 (Box 57, Folder 1168 - 1169)
  - Classical department, 1920-1951 (Box 57, Folder 1170)
  - Directed studies, 1947-1957 (Box 57, Folder 1171 - 1173)
  - Directed studies project, 1956-1957 (Box 57, Folder 1174 - 1175)
  - Engineering department - electrical, 1921-1922 (Box 57, Folder 1176)
  - Economics dept, 1940-1956 (Box 57, Folder 1177)
  - Engineering departments - general, 1920-1956 (Box 57, Folder 1178)
  - Engineering departments - electrical, 1920-1921 (Box 57, Folder 1179)
  - Engineering departments - mining & metallurgy, 1920-1921 (Box 57, Folder 1180)
  - English department, 1920-1957 (Box 57, Folder 1181)
  - French department, 1931-1957 (Box 57, Folder 1182)
  - General, 1920-1921 (Box 57, Folder 1183)
  - Departments general, 1921-1922 (Box 57, Folder 1184)
  - General, 1922-1937 (Box 58, Folder 1185 - 1199)
  - Departments' general, 1937-1938 (Box 58, Folder 1200)
  - General, 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 1201)
  - Departments - general, 1939-1940 (Box 58, Folder 1202)
  - General (all depts.), 1940-1942 (Box 58, Folder 1203 - 1204)
  - General, 1942-1943 (Box 58, Folder 1205)
  - General (all depts), 1943-1945 (Box 58, Folder 1206 - 1207)
  - General, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 1208)
  - General (all departments), 1946-1952 (Box 58, Folder 1209 - 1214)
  - General, 1952-1955 (Box 58, Folder 1215 - 1217)
  - General (all departments), 1955-1957 (Box 58, Folder 1218 - 1219)
  - Geography department, 1950-1951 (Box 59, Folder 1220)
  - Geology dept, 1935-1957 (Box 59, Folder 1221)
  - Germanic department, 1920-1949 (Box 59, Folder 1222)
  - Gymnasium, 1921-1933 (Box 59, Folder 1223)
  - Health department, 1920-1936 (Box 59, Folder 1224)
  - History department, 1920-1957 (Box 59, Folder 1225)
  - History department library, 1920-1929 (Box 59, Folder 1226)
  - History of art dept, 1952-1956 (Box 59, Folder 1227)
  - Italian instruction, 1935-1936 (Box 59, Folder 1228)
  - Mathematic department, 1920-1923 (Box 59, Folder 1229)
  - Military science department, 1920-1923 (Box 59, Folder 1230)
  - Mathematics department, 1923-1957 (Box 59, Folder 1231)
  - Military science department, 1924-1957 (Box 59, Folder 1232 - 1234)
  - Music dept. (1939-1947) (Box 59, Folder 1235)
  - Naval science department, 1926-1933 (Box 59, Folder 1236 - 1242)
  - Naval science department, 1933-1952 (Box 60, Folder 1243 - 1249)
  - Naval bulletins, 1947-1950 (Box 60, Folder 1250 - 1252)
  - Philosophy, 1944-1949 (Box 60, Folder 1253)
  - Naval science dept, 1952-1957 (Box 60, Folder 1254 - 1259)
  - Physics department, 1920-1945 (Box 60, Folder 1260)
  - Physiology department, 1942-1943 (Box 60, Folder 1261)
  - Physics department, 1946-1952 (Box 60, Folder 1262)
  - Philosophy department, 1950-1953 (Box 60, Folder 1263)
  - Physics department, 1952-1953 (Box 60, Folder 1264)
  - Political science department, 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 1265)
  - Psychology department, 1952-1957 (Box 60, Folder 1266)
  - Romance department, 1920-1930 (Box 60, Folder 1267)
  - Religion department, 1952-1953 (Box 60, Folder 1268)
  - Science: (I, II, III), 1947-1954 (Box 60, Folder 1269 - 1270)
  - Sociology department, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 1271)
  - Social sciences course, 1923-1925 (Box 61, Folder 1272 - 1273)
  - Social sciences, 1925-1926 (Box 61, Folder 1274)
  - Spanish department, 1930-1936 (Box 61, Folder 1275)
  - Spanish, Italian department, 1946-1950 (Box 61, Folder 1276)
  - Zoology department, 1921-1956 (Box 61, Folder 1277)
  - A, 1920-1957 (Box 62, Folder 1278 - 1279)
  - Advanced placement - general, 1954-195762 (Box 62, Folder 1280 - 1282)
  - Alumni affairs, 1920-1957 (Box 62, Folder 1283 - 1286)
  - Alumni university fund association, 1920-1924 (Box 62, Folder 1287)
  - Alumni committee of Yale University, 1920-1921 (Box 62, Folder 1288)
  - Assn. of American Universities, 1921-1923 (Box 62, Folder 1289)
  - B, 1920-1957 (Box 62, Folder 1290 - 1291)
  - C, 1920-1952 (Box 62, Folder 1292)
  - College entrance exam board, 1952-1953 (Box 62, Folder 1293)
  - College entrance examination board, 1947-1950 (Box 62, Folder 1294)
  - College entrance exam, 1950-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1295)
  - Curiosities, 1921-1922 (Box 63, Folder 1296)
  - D, 1920-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1297 - 1298)
  - E, 1920-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1299)
  - Ex-freshmen, 1921-1943 (Box 63, Folder 1300 - 1304)
  - Ex-freshmen, 1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 1305 - 1306)
  - Ex-freshmen: general, 1944-1947 (Box 64, Folder 1307 - 1311)
  - Ex-freshmen: general, 1946-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1312 - 1318)
  - Ex-freshmen (civilian and navy), 1951-1952 (Box 65, Folder 1319)
  - Ex-freshmen, 1952-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1320)
  - Ex-freshmen post-war plans, 1944-1945 (Box 66, Folder 1321)
  - Ex-freshmen-post-war plans for return to Yale, 1945-1946 (Box 66, Folder 1322)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1937-1938 (Box 66, Folder 1323)
  - F, 1920-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1324)
  - Freshmen year book, 1922-1925 (Box 66, Folder 1325)
  - Fraternities, 1920-1930 (Box 66, Folder 1326)
  - G, 1920-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1327)
  - H, 1920-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1328 - 1329)
  - Harvard, 1921-1926 (Box 66, Folder 1330)
  - I, 1920-1950 (Box 66, Folder 1331)
  - Insured tuition payments plan, 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1332)
  - J, 1920-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1333)
  - K, 1920-1950 (Box 67, Folder 1334)
  - L, 1920-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1335)
  - M, 1920-1923 (Box 67, Folder 1336)
  - Mc, 1928-1956 (Box 67, Folder 1337)
  - M, 1925-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1338)
  - Mc, 1920-1922 (Box 67, Folder 1339)
  - N, 1920-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1340)
  - New England Association of College Presidents, 1930-1931 (Box 67, Folder 1341)
  - Navy trainees - previously enrolled, 1946-1947 (Box 67, Folder 1342 - 1344)
  - Navy trainees, 1947-1948 (Box 67, Folder 1345)
  - Navy trainees previously enrolled, 1948-1951 (Box 67, Folder 1346 - 1348)
  - Navy (NROTC) bulletins, 1946-1947 (Box 68, Folder 1349)
  - O, 1920-1950 (Box 68, Folder 1350)
  - P, 1920-1957 (Box 68, Folder 1351)
  - Parents, letters to, 1922-1932 (Box 68, Folder 1352)
  - Parents letters, 1925-1926 (Box 68, Folder 1353)
  - Positions and recommendations, 1920-1955 (Box 68, Folder 1354 - 1357)
  - Prospects for 1950-1951, 1950-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1358)
  - President-elect, 1920-1921 (Box 69, Folder 1359)
  - Progressive Education Assn., 1937-1940 (Box 69, Folder 1360)
  - Publications, undergraduate, 1920-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1361 - 1362)
  - Q, 1920-1921 (Box 69, Folder 1363)
  - R, 1920-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1364)
  - Riot of May 1928, 1928-1929 (Box 69, Folder 1365)
  - S, 1920-1957 (Box 69, Folder 1366 - 1367)
  - Secondary school relations, 1920-1921 (Box 69, Folder 1368)
  - Secondary school relations - general, 1921-1922 (Box 69, Folder 1369)
  - Secondary school relations: report of students to midterm April 2, 1921, 1920-1921 (Box 69, Folder 1370)
  - Secondary school relations: report of students to midyear, 1920-1921 (Box 70, Folder 1371)
  - Secondary school relations: report of students to June 1921, 1920-1921 (Box 70, Folder 1372)
  - Secondary school relations - comments to students to mid-years, 1921-1922 (Box 70, Folder 1373 - 1374)
  - Secondary school relations midyears -June, 1921-1922 (Box 70, Folder 1375)
  - Secondary school relations - general, 1922-1923 (Box 70, Folder 1376)
  - Secondary school relations reports on preparatory schools, 1922-1923 (Box 70, Folder 1377)
  - Secondary school relations, 1937-1938 (Box 70, Folder 1378)
  - Secondary school relations - general, 1938-1939 (Box 70, Folder 1379)
  - Secondary school relations (letters re: Academic Guest Suite), 1938-1939 (Box 70, Folder 1380)
  - Secondary school relations - general, 1923-1925 (Box 70, Folder 1381)
  - Secondary school relations - general, 1925-1948 (Box 71, Folder 1382 - 1388)
  - Secondary school relations -general, 1948-1957 (Box 72, Folder 1389 - 1391)
  - Secondary school relations: comments on students data on records, 1924-1937 (Box 72, Folder 1392 - 1393)
  - Secondary school relations recommendations on better students, 1927-1933 (Box 72, Folder 1394)
  - Secondary school relations - academic guest suite, 1939-1950 (Box 72, Folder 1395)
  - Secondary school relations: on planning a course, 1954-1957 (Box 72, Folder 1396)
  - T, 1920-1951 (Box 72, Folder 1397)
  - Tutoring schools, 1929-1930 (Box 72, Folder 1398)
  - V, 1923-1957 (Box 72, Folder 1399 - 1400)
  - W, 1920-1957 (Box 73, Folder 1401)
  - Western trip, 1920-1921 (Box 73, Folder 1402)
  - X - Y - Z, 1920-1955 (Box 73, Folder 1403 - 1417)
  - Yale blue book (filed 1922-1923 "freshman year book"), 1921-1922 (Box 73, Folder 1418)
  - Yale system of selective study, 1921-1922 (Box 73, Folder 1419)
  - Yale Aeronautical Society, 1927-1930 (Box 73, Folder 1420 - 1422)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1934-1936 (Box 73, Folder 1423 - 1424)
  - Indices, 1957-1961 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - A, 1957-1963 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Academic freedom 1955-1956, 1955-1956, 1960, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Accounts, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Admissions and student appointments: office of counseling, placement and research, 1957-1959 (Box 74, Folder 5 - 6)
  - Admissions and student appointments, office of, 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Admissions and student appointments (counseling, placement and research, 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Admissions and student appointments: counseling and placement, 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Admissions - counseling & placement, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Admissions and student appointments: counseling and placement, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Admissions and student appointments; educational research; research coordinating committee, 1961-1962 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Admissions - educational research co-ordinating committee, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Admissions and student appointments: educational research co-ordinating committee, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Admissions and student appointments: financial Aid Office, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Admissions & student appointments - financial Aids Office (incl. F.A. Committee), 1958-1962 (Box 74, Folder 16 - 18)
  - Admissions - Financial Aids Office - financial aids committee, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Admissions and student appointments: Financial Aid and Financial Aid Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Admissions & student appointments & freshman scholarships, 1957-1958 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Admissions & student appointments - office of admissions & freshman scholarships, 1958-1959 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Admissions and student appointments, (admissions & freshman scholarship), 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Admissions and freshman scholarship committee on enrollment and scholarship, 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Admissions and student appointments: administration and freshman scholarships including enrollment and scholarships committee, 1961-1962 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Admissions office & enrollment and scholarship, 1962-1963 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Admissions and student appointments: office of admissions and freshman scholarships, 1963-1964 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Admissions, enrollment and scholarship committee, 1963-1964 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Admissions and student appointments & governing board, 1957-1963 (Box 75, Folder 29 - 31)
  - Admissions office: southern trip (Harold B. Whiteman), 1963-1964 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Advanced placement - college credits, 1962-1964 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Advanced placement commission, 1957-1960 (Box 75, Folder 34 - 36)
  - Advanced placement commission: miscellaneous mimeographed material, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Advanced placement committees, 1957-1961 (Box 75, Folder 38 - 41)
  - Advanced placement committees, 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - Advanced placement conference, (Yale), 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - Advanced placement conferences, 1958-1963 (Box 76, Folder 44 - 47)
  - Advanced placement conference June, Yale: account, 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Advanced placement conferences: June 1958, Yale: correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 49)
  - Advanced placement conference (non-yale), 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 50)
  - Advanced placement conference: Brandeis, 1959-1960 (Box 76, Folder 51)
  - Advanced placement conferences: Lawrenceville, 1959-1960 (Box 76, Folder 52)
  - Advanced placement: distributional credits, 1963-1964 (Box 76, Folder 53)
  - Advanced placement exams, 1957-1958 (Box 76, Folder 54)
  - A.P. Examinations, 1958-1959 (Box 76, Folder 55)
  - Advanced placement examinations, 1959-1964 (Box 77, Folder 56 - 60)
  - Advanced placement (miscellaneous correspondence and other material), 1958-1959 (Box 77, Folder 61)
  - Advanced placement: miscellaneous correspondence with colleges and schools, 1959-1962 (Box 77, Folder 62 - 63)
  - Advanced placement: miscellaneous correspondence and other material, 1957-1960 (Box 77, Folder 64 - 65)
  - Advanced placement: miscellaneous correspondence and other material, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 66)
  - Advanced placement - miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 78, Folder 67)
  - Advanced placement: miscellaneous correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 78, Folder 68)
  - Advanced placement program June 1957, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 69)
  - Advanced placement statistics, 1957-1964 (Box 78, Folder 70 - 75)
  - Advisory committee, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 76)
  - Albertus mixer, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 77)
  - Allocations, class of 1966, 1962-1963 (Box 78, Folder 78 - 80)
  - Allocations, class of 1966, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 81)
  - Allocations (college): including charges against council of masters, 1957-1960 (Box 79, Folder 82 - 84)
  - Alpha Phi Omega, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 85)
  - Alumni affairs (including Yale Alumni Weekly ), 1957-1961 (Box 79, Folder 86)
  - Alumni board, 1961-1964 (Box 79, Folder 87 - 89)
  - Alumni music committee, 1958-1959 (Box 79, Folder 90)
  - American council on education, 1960-1961 (Box 79, Folder 91)
  - Associate student agencies, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 92)
  - Athletic activities, 1962-1964 (Box 79, Folder 93 - 94)
  - Athletic association and athletics, miscellaneous, 1957-1961 (Box 79, Folder 95 - 98)
  - Athletic association and athlectics miscellaneous: Ivy group committee, 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 99)
  - Athletic board of control, 1962-1963 (Box 79, Folder 100)
  - Athletic board of control, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 101)
  - Atlanta, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 102)
  - Aurelian honor society, 1958-1964 (Box 80, Folder 103)
  - B, 1957-1958 (Box 80, Folder 104)
  - Basement rooms, 1960-1964 (Box 80, Folder 105 - 108)
  - Bingham game room, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 109)
  - Buckley, William F., 1954-1957 (Box 80, Folder 110)
  - Budget, freshman year, 1957-1963 (Box 80, Folder 111)
  - Bulletin board notices, 1957-1964 (Box 80, Folder 112)
  - Bursar, 1957-1964 (Box 80, Folder 113)
  - Business manager, 1957-1961 (Box 80, Folder 114)
  - Buttery, 1958-1964 (Box 80, Folder 115 - 120)
  - C, 1957-1959 (Box 80, Folder 121)
  - Cambell, Robert W., fund gift no.2816, 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 122)
  - Calendar university, 1957-1964 (Box 80, Folder 123)
  - Campus police, 1957-1961 (Box 81, Folder 124 - 128)
  - Carnegie studies program, 1957-1964 (Box 81, Folder 129)
  - Class of 1967 - by students with home address, 1962-1963 (Box 81, Folder 130)
  - Coffee hour, 1957-1960 (Box 82, Folder 131)
  - College credits, 1957-1962 (Box 82, Folder 132)
  - College deans, 1962-1964 (Box 82, Folder 133 - 134)
  - College discussion courses, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 135)
  - College entrance examination board, 1957-1964 (Box 82, Folder 136 - 143)
  - Committee on parietal rules, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 144)
  - Committees, miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 145)
  - Commons and other dinning halls, 1957-1963 (Box 82, Folder 146 - 151)
  - Commons and other dinning halls, 1963-1964 (Box 83, Folder 152)
  - Comptroller's office, 1958-1964 (Box 83, Folder 153)
  - Council of masters, 1958-1964 (Box 83, Folder 154 - 159)
  - Counseling program, 1957-1959 (Box 83, Folder 160 - 161)
  - Counseling program: inquiries about our system, 1959-1960 (Box 83, Folder 162)
  - Counseling program: our registration, 1959-1960 (Box 83, Folder 163)
  - Counseling program: counseling, placement, and research, 1960-1961 (Box 84, Folder 164)
  - Counseling program: office of counseling and placement, 1961-196284 (Box 84, Folder 165)
  - Counselors, general, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 166)
  - Counselors: letters, circulars and notices to, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 167)
  - Counselors: miscellaneous remarks, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 168)
  - Counselors: circular letters and notices to, 1958-1959 (Box 84, Folder 169)
  - Counselors, general, 1958-1959 (Box 84, Folder 170)
  - Counselors: miscellaneous remarks of, 1958-1959 (Box 84, Folder 171)
  - Counselors, 1959-1962 (Box 84, Folder 172 - 174)
  - Counselors, 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 175 - 176)
  - Counselor applicants for 1960-1961 general information, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 177)
  - Counselor's applications, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 178)
  - Counselors & college affiliation with students listed below, 1962-1963 (Box 85, Folder 179)
  - Counselor comments, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 180)
  - Counselors for 1961-1962, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 181)
  - Counselors for 1962-1963, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 182)
  - Counselor information, 1963-1964 (Box 85, Folder 183 - 184)
  - Counselors, letters, notices, circulars, 1959-1960 (Box 85, Folder 185)
  - Counselors - letters, circulars & notices to, 1960-1962 (Box 85, Folder 186 - 187)
  - Counselors - letter and notices sent to, 1962-1963 (Box 85, Folder 188)
  - Counselors - letters and notices, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 189)
  - Counselors - miscellaneous remarks of, 1959-1961 (Box 86, Folder 190 - 191)
  - Counselor meetings, 1957-1964 (Box 86, Folder 192)
  - Counselor report blank - suggestions, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 193)
  - Course & instructor evaluation, 1958-1962 (Box 86, Folder 194 - 197)
  - Course of study committee, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 198)
  - Cut reports, 1960-1961 (Box 86, Folder 199)
  - D, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 200)
  - Dances, 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 201)
  - Mixer dances, 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 202)
  - Dances: dances and mixers, 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 203)
  - Dances, 1959-1960 (Box 86, Folder 204)
  - Dances: dances and mixers, 1959-1960 (Box 86, Folder 205)
  - Dances: day school mixer, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 206)
  - Dances: Dartmouth dance, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 207)
  - Dances: Harvard dance, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 208)
  - Dances: dances and mixers, 1960-1961 (Box 86, Folder 209)
  - Dances, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 210)
  - Dances: dances and mixers, 1961-1962 (Box 86, Folder 211)
  - Dances, 1962-1963 (Box 87, Folder 212)
  - Dances: Dances and mixers, 1962-1963 (Box 87, Folder 213)
  - Dances, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 214)
  - The Day, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 215)
  - Dean's fund: Dean's special fund, 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 216)
  - Dean's fund, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 217)
  - Dean's fund, freshman, 1959-1963 (Box 87, Folder 218 - 221)
  - Dean's loan and gift fund, 1957-1959 (Box 87, Folder 222 - 223)
  - Dean's gift & loan funds and Dyer fund, 1959-1963 (Box 87, Folder 224 - 227)
  - Dean's gift and loan funds, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 228)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1959-1964 (Box 87, Folder 229)
  - Departments of study - Chemistry, 1958-1959 (Box 87, Folder 230)
  - Departments of study: Math, 1957-1960 (Box 87, Folder 231)
  - Departments of study - military science, 1958-1963 (Box 88, Folder 232 - 236)
  - Departments of study -military service, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 237)
  - Department of study, miscellaneous, 1957-1964 (Box 88, Folder 238 - 244)
  - Department of study: Naval science, 1957-1964 (Box 88, Folder 245 - 251)
  - Development, University, 1959-1963 (Box 89, Folder 252 - 255)
  - Development office, 1958-1959 (Box 89, Folder 256)
  - Directed studies program, 1957-1963 (Box 89, Folder 257 - 262)
  - Discussion groups - class 1960, 1957-1958 (Box 90, Folder 263)
  - Discussion groups: lawyers, 1961-1962 (Box 90, Folder 264)
  - Distribution credits, 1957-1963 (Box 90, Folder 265 - 269)
  - Dormitory rooms, 1957-1961 (Box 90, Folder 270)
  - Durfee recreation room, 1958-1961 (Box 90, Folder 271)
  - E, 1959-1963 (Box 90, Folder 272)
  - Education, committee on, general, 1954-1957 (Box 90, Folder 273)
  - Educational T.V., 1960 (Box 90, Folder 274)
  - Eligibility (athletics), 1953-1962 (Box 90, Folder 275)
  - Engineering school, 1957-1962 (Box 90, Folder 276 - 279)
  - Enrollment and scholarships (committee, alumni representatives, miscellaneous), 1957-1960 (Box 90, Folder 280 - 282)
  - Equipment and facilities, 1957-1964 (Box 90, Folder 283 - 289)
  - Executive committee (Yale College), 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 290)
  - Executive committee of the faculty of arts and sciences, 1957-1962 (Box 91, Folder 291 - 295)
  - Yale College executive committee, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 296)
  - F, 1957-1964 (Box 91, Folder 297)
  - Faculty advisers, 1957-1963 (Box 91, Folder 298 - 304)
  - Faculty program advisers, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 305)
  - Faculty advisers, questionnaire on, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 306)
  - Faculty adviser questionnaire, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 307)
  - Financial aids officer including financial aid committee, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 308)
  - Foreign students, 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 309)
  - Freshman activities committee, 1957-1959 (Box 92, Folder 310 - 311)
  - Freshman activities committee: future freshman classes, 1958-1959 (Box 92, Folder 312)
  - Freshman activities committee, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 313)
  - Freshman activities committee: Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 314)
  - Freshman activities committee: selection, 1959-1960 (Box 92, Folder 315)
  - Freshman activities committee, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 316)
  - Freshman activities committee files, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 317)
  - Freshman activities committee, 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 318 - 319)